Mystery of the Police Car Robot!
I almost had it...
Hm?
Ah! I'm gonna be late for school!
Huh, what's that?
A... robot?
This ends now, Mega Trucker!
You're coming with me.
Do you really think I'm just gonna play along nicely?!
Look alive, I'm not done yet!
This stubborn truck...!
My BMX!
There's a human here!
Tch. This isn't over!
Stop right there!
What have you done to my bike?!
And where did my helmet go?
Hey, we'll be in middle school next year and you're still saying things like,
"I saw a robot! I saw an alien!"
I think he's finally lost it!
Vance, you sounded just like him!
I swear I saw it with my own two eyes!
A police car transformed into a robot!
Oh really? Then where's your proof, huh?
Ughh...
Look at my crushed BMX!
Huh... sorry, but it looks like you fell off and broke your bike.
Ah! So he made up a whole story just to blame a robot for that? Vance, you're sharp!
You should have made up a more believable story, Jun.
I don't think he's lying.
Huh?
And what do you mean by that, class president?
Are you trying to say that Vance is wrong?!
I know Jun isn't one to tell petty lies like that.
As expected of Anna! You're the only one who believes in me!
I think he's probably just mistaken.
Ugh... she didn't believe me either...
I believe your robot story.
Theo!
Security cameras?
If what you said is true, something must have been caught on video!
Alright!
Huh?
Yeah, so when I got here this morning, I saw-
Huh? Jun!
Jun, you're safe and sound!
Stop it! I can't breathe!
I was worried sick! When I got here this morning, this place was a mess!
And then I found your bike and thought you got crushed too!
Hehe... Sorry for worrying you.
It's okay. Thank you.
We'll be heading back to the station now.
Thanks for stopping by!
Here you go.
Tell me, what brings you guys here?
Show us the security footage!
Huh?
Right there!
Rewind a little bit, please!
This doesn't show us anything...
Yeah, didn't even get the license plate.
It would be nice to know the license plate for the police car-
And what would you do with that? Would you go to the police station and ask,
"Is there a car here that transforms into a robot?"
I knew it! You don't believe me either!
Who would believe something like that?
If only there was some other clue...
Hang on! I have this!
I picked it up after all of that happened.
Did the robots leave it behind?
I think so.
This looks like something you can buy anywhere these days.
Stop messing around...
Agh, I'm not! I really can't lift it! It's like it's glued to the table!
Let me try.
I can't move it at all, not even an inch!
Don't be ridiculous. See?
Agh! What's going on here?!
That's what I should be asking you...
Let's go look for a place where a dump truck might be parked.
You guys never give up, do you?
Are you sure you're not just trying to impress Anna?
That's not it!
I'll be back soon!
And throw away that strange watch, will you?
Alright, alright.
Ugh... guess it wouldn't be that easy to find, right?
There's no guarantee it'll even be in this town anymore.
Stop it!
Anna?!
You got a problem, class president?
Don't act so high-and-mighty just because you're head of the student council!
I'm not! You're being vandals by painting over our city without permission!
That's what I call acting high-and-mighty!
Why do you care so much about this city? You want to get sprayed too?!
Don't!
Back off!
J-Jun?
Heh! So you want to play the hero?
How's the robot hunt going?
I'll find it soon!
You sound confident!
I stepped in poop.
Rapid fire poop kick!!
Get away, get away!
Vance! How dare you! Aah!
You really fell for it!
- See you later, Anna!
- Jun!
Get back here!
I said stop! Hey!!
You're so dead when we catch you!
-Ravi!
-On it!
Ta-da!
Waahh! Not good!
Nice try!
Nowhere to run now!
Hang on! Let's not resort to violence, you guys!
Shut up!
Hey! Give that back!
This is for trying to trick me!
Hey!
Quit struggling!
I said, stop it!
What's going on?
What are you trying to pull now?!
Change... Up!
Is that... the robot from before...? (FX-italic)
Wha...
A robot! Jun was telling the truth!
Come on, that's impossible!
You must be seeing things!
But you saw it too, Vance...
Listen up! You better not tell anyone about this,
unless you want to be called a liar too, got it?
Alright...
W-What's going on?!
How is it driving by itself?!
Nice to meet you.
Huh?
I am Blue Cop, from the planet Machina.
Blue Cop?
Agh! So does that mean I'm inside a robot's stomach right now?
Help, I've been eaten by a robot!!
Huh? What's the matter?
Get me out before I'm digested!
Digested?
Wait, not out the backside. Spit me back up!
I am a mechanical lifeform. I do not digest nor excrete.
Oh, really?
It's going to get a little bumpy.
Aah!
My home planet, Machina, was completely destroyed in a giant explosion.
Destroyed?
Ever since arriving on this planet, I have pretended to be a car so as not to alarm the natives.
As your kind says, a tree is best hidden in a forest.
I'm surprised you know that saying...
I have to live on Earth now.
So I am trying my best to learn as much about this planet as I can.
I like this planet very much.
However, there are some of my kind who have not adjusted to life here yet.
You mean, like that dump truck from yesterday?
He's not the only one.
There are more Metal Cardbots hiding on Earth who I have yet to identify.
I only wish to help them, so that they do not harm the natives of this planet. If I don't succeed,
Wait, wait, wait! Why are you telling me all this?
Because it looks like the Metal Breath chose you, sir.
Metal Breath?
The Metal Breath can only be possessed by the chosen one.
It is said that the one who wields the Metal Breath will become the king that will shackle all of the Metal Cardbots.
K-king?
Uh! Pardon my mistake. I mean... the boss? The master?
So, you mean... someone important?
Yes sir! That's correct.
No way! I haven't even been class president or anything!
Please. I ask that you lend me your strength, sir.
Hmm... alright!
But on one condition!
What's that?
My name is Jun Grant! Call me Jun, not sir!
Yes, Jun!
And one more thing!
My BMX that your friend crushed! You'll need to compensate me for that!
What?!